The Peter Bekker Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Peter Bekker, Jr.
  - Subseries 1.8 Audio Recordings, Cassettes are organized alphabetically
    - Subseries 1.8.1 Cassettes
      - [Saint] Saint, Artist: Saint Length: 00:12:47 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.2.wav, 1.8.1.14.2.mp3 (Box 14, Cassette 2)
      - [Saffan, Mark] Peter Bernstein/Mark Goldenberg Cretones 3/2/81 EA/KA Mark Case- Plimsouls ditto Mark Saffan 3/2/81 EA/LA, 0:01:05; Artist: Mark Saffan Length: 00:01:05 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.28.mp3, 1.8.1.11.28.wav (Box 11, Cassette 28)
      - [Sampler] Various New Music Artists \ Side One: PETER WOLF Oo-Ee-Diddley Bop!/MELODY MAKERS Raggae Is Now/SILENT RUNNING Emotional Warfare/HELLYBEAN The Mexican/PSUEDO ECHO Listening**/CHEQUERED PAST How Much Is Too Much?/JOHN WAITE Missing You/PETER TOSH Get Up, Stand Up*/THE RED HOT CHILI PEPPERS True Men Don't Kill Coyotes \ Side Two:NAKED EYES (What) In The Name Of Love*/COREY HART Sunglasses At Night/LITTLE STEVEN Undefeated (Everybody Goes Home)/THE ARMOURY SHOW Castles In Spain/THE DEL-LORDS Burnin' In The Flame OfLove/PRIVATE LIVES Living In A World (Turned Upside Down)*/ANTHONY MORE Industrial Drums*/TALKTALK Dum DUm Girl*/JASON AND THE SCORCHERS Honky Tonk Blues (Live At Irving Plaza, NYC on March 8, 1984), Artist: Various Length: 00:29:55 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.3.mp3, 1.8.1.14.3.wav (Box 14, Cassette 3)
      - [Sardenberg, Sergio]Sergio Sardenberg 2/9//87, Artist: Sergio Sardenberg Length: 00:29:35 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.4.mp3, 1.8.1.14.4.wav (Box 14, Cassette 4)
      - [Scaggs, Boz] Boz/Let's Go, Artist: Boz Scaggs Length: 00:45:48 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.5.mp3, 1.8.1.14.5.wav (Box 14, Cassette 5)
      - [Scandal] Rickie Lee/ The Magazine /Scandal, Artist: Scandal Length: 01:31:24 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.3.mp3, 1.8.1.13.3.wav (Box 13, Cassette 3)
      - [Schubert, Franz] Japan- Shubert #8 Bomm/LvB#5 (1+4), Artist: Franz Shubert Length: 00:52:19 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.6.mp3, 1.8.1.14.6.wav (Box 14, Cassette 6)
      - [Scott,Tom] TOM SCOTT- PAUL COLLINS/BOB GELDOFF- SHEEN MEMORIAL 5 TOM SCOTT/berkshire pl hotel #1521 12/7/79 * MEMORIAL FOR FULTON SHEET/st. pat's 12/10 cooke + McGarrick PAUL COLLINS/(the beat) WCBS 12/12 BOB GELDORF (boomtown rats) berkshire pl hotel #908 12/14/79 5, Artist: Tom Scott Length: 01:38:12 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.16.mp3, 1.8.1.12.16.wav (Box 12, Cassette 16)
      - [Shakuhachi] Shakuhachi / Laurie Anderson, Artist: Shakuhachi Length: 01:03:57 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.5.mp3, 1.8.1.11.5.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 5)
      - [Simon, Paul] Paul Simon - Rhythm of the Saints \Lyle Lovett\ Side a: The obvious child - cant run the but the coast - further to fly - she moves on - Born the right time - The cool cool river spirit voices - Rhythm of the saints \Side b: If I had a boat - Give back my heart - I loved you yesterday - Walk thru the broken land - LA County - She's no lady - Money - Black + Blue - Simple Song - Pontiac - Shes Hot to Go, Artist: Paul Simon Length: 01:23:51 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.15.mp3, 1.8.1.13.15.wav (Box 13, Cassette 15)
      - [Simmons, Gene] Gene Simmons /Nona Hendry x Blotto /Alabama, Artist: Gene Simmons Length: 01:24:43 Type: Interview File Names: 1.7.1.11.2.mp3, 1.7.1.11.2.wav (Box 11, Cassette 2)
      - [Simmons, Patrick] Patrick Simmons - 4/7/1983 Elektra - la David Bellamy merv griffin theatre Andy Pierce Epic records 4/8 Carl Wilson rogers & cowan 4/12, Artist: Patrick Simmons Length: 01:30:39 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.27.mp3, 1.8.1.11.27.wav (Box 11, Cassette 27)
      - [Simple Minds] Lena Lovich 4/13/83 epic la Simple minds 4/15 a&m la Kiddo 4/15/83 a&m la Whispers 4/15 elektra la, Artist: Simple Minds Length: 01:40:29 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.12.26.mp3, 1.8.1.12.26.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 26)
      - [Simon, Paul] Trio Harris Parton Ronstadt Graceland Paul Simon, Artist: Paul Simon Length: 01:26:48 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.7.mp3, 1.8.1.14.7.wav (Box 14, Cassette 7)
      - [Simone, Mark] Mark Simone 494 History of Top 40, Artist: Mark Simone Length: 00:06:16 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.8.mp3, 1.8.1.14.8.wav (Box 14, Cassette 8)
      - [Simone, Mark] Mark Simone - "Simone Phone" Contact: Adam Berg- WM. Morris, Artist: Mark Simone Length: 00:31:05 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.9.mp3, 1.8..1.14.9.wav (Box 14, Cassette 9)
      - [Springsteen, Bruce] Bruce Springsteen - Born in the USA Sgt. Pepper, Artist: Bruce Springsteen Length: 01:34:45 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.18.mp3, 1.8.1.11.19.wav (Box 11, Cassette 1)
      - [Steely Dan] Steely Dan / Afrika, Artist: Steely Dan/Africa Length: 01:31:31 Type: Music File Names: 1.7.1.11.1.mp3, 1.7.1.11.2.wav (Box 11, Cassette 19)
      - [Talking Heads] Talking Heads - Sense Divan, Artist: Divan Length: 01:32:05 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.26.mp3, 1.8.1.12.26.wav (Box 12, Cassette 26)
      - [Thomason, Richie] Demo: Music Box Special Monday 6:44 Tuesday 6:32 Wednesday 6:15 Thursday 7:18 Friday 6:3, Artist: Richie Thomason Length: 00:35:47 Type: 00:35:47 File Names: 1.8.1.14.10.mp3, 1.8.14.10.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.17 cassette for J-Card (Box 14, Cassette 10)
      - [Tillis, Pam] Bill Lamb 6/23/83 wb-Nashville\ Pam Tillis 6/23/83 WB- Nashville, Artist: Pam Tillis Length: 01:20:41 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.13.13.mp3, 1.8.1.13.13.wav (Box 13, Cassette 13)
      - [Tommy Tutone] Translator Laurie Anderson Tommy Tutone, Artist: Tomy Tutone Length: 01:335:42 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.4.mp3, 1.8.1.11.4.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 4)
      - [Translator] Translator Laurie Anderson Tommy Tutone, Artist: Translator Length: 01:335:42 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.4.mp3, 1.8.1.11.4.wav See Folder 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 11, Cassette 4)
      - [Trio] Trio Harris Parton Ronstadt Graceland Paul Simon, Artist: Paul Simon Length: 01:26:48 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.7.mp3, 1.8.1.14.7.wav (Box 14, Cassette 7)
      - [UB 40] UB40 - Jeff Morgan King Sunny Ade, Artist: King Sunny Ade Length: 0:21:56 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.4.mp3, 1.8.1.13.4.wav (Box 13, Cassette 4)
      - [Unknown] 45's, Artist: Unknown Length: 01:26:05 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.11.mp3, 1.8.1.14.11.wav (Box 14, Cassette 11)
      - [Unknown] Blackbird, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:04:25 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.12.mp3, 1.8.1.14.12.wav (Box 14, Cassette 12)
      - [Unknown] Casio Ramblings, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:31:23 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.13.mp3, 1.8.1.14.13.wav (Box 14, Cassette 13)
      - [Unknown] Ennui, Mostly. Plantation Favorites, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:49:14 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.14.mp3, 1.8.1.14.14.wav (Box 14, Cassette 14)
      - [Unknown] Interviews - Bitter End Rename Bitter End, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:32:38 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.15.mp3, 1.8.1.14.15.wav (Box 14, Cassette 15)
      - [Unknown] Long Black Veil, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:19:49 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.16.mp3, 1.8.1.14.16.wav (Box 14, Cassette 16)
      - [Unknown] Original Stuff, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:49:14 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.17.mp3, 1.8.1.14.17.wav (Box 14, Cassette 17)
      - [Unknown] Parson & Farnsworth Impersonator 11/4 2:00, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:02:18 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.18.mp3, 1.8.1.14.18.wav (Box 14, Cassette 18)
      - [Unknown] Respectable Rock/ Disco Rock, Artist: Unknown Length: 01:35:53 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.19.mp3, 1.8.1.14.19.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for cassette J-Card (Box 14, Cassette 19)
      - [Unknown] Song Bites, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:16:30 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.20.mp3, 1.8.1.14.20.wav (Box 14, Cassette 20)
      - [Martin, John] Ventures/John Martin, Artist: John Martin Length: 00:41:17 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.13.18.mp3, 1.8.1.13.18.wav (Box 13, Cassette 18)
      - [Ventures] DC 5/Ventures/Brenda Lee, Artist: Ventures Length: 00:46:16 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.19.mp3, 1.8.1.12.19.wav (Box 12, Cassette 19)
      - [Wallace, Mike] CBS Radio Mike Wallace "1939" "Remembering 1939" Mike Wallace 6 Pieces May 1989, Artist: Mike Wallace Length: 00:14:03 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.21.mp3, 1.8.1.14.21.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for cassette J-Card (Box 14, Cassette 21)
      - [Whispers] Lena Lovich 4/13/83 epic la Simple minds 4/15 a&m la Kiddo 4/15/83 a&m la Whispers 4/15 elektra la, Artist: Whispers Length: 01:40:29 Type: Interview File Names: 1.8.1.12.26.mp3, 1.8.1.12.26.wav See folder PBP 1.8.1.6.15 for cassette J-Card (Box 12, Cassette 26)
      - [Wilson, Joey] 4 Seasons/ Hodge Podge \J. Mitchell Real Good For Free \ T. Waits On the Nickel \4 Seasons Itzhak Porchan/London Phil Hodge Podge \J. Jackson --> Steppin Out \John Prince --> SABU visits the twin cities alone \ Dan Hicks / Hot Lix O'Reilly @ the bar \ Steve Goodman Sdrawv. Cab Klat \Evrythmics Sweet Dreams \Joey Wilson If you dont want my love \ J. Browne Lawyers in Love \Dire Straits Romeo + Juliet, 1:26:54; Artist: Joey Wilson Length: 01:26:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.11.36.mp3, 1.8.1.11.36.wav (Box 11, Cassette 36)
      - [Wilson, Carl] Patrick Simmons - 4/7/1983 Elektra - la David Bellamy merv griffin theatre Andy Pierce Epic records 4/8 Carl Wilson rogers & cowan 4/12, Artist: Carl Wilson Length: 01:30:39 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.11.27.mp3, 1.8.1.11.27.wav (Box 11, Cassette 27)
      - [Winter, Johnny] Johnny Winter - 3rd degree, Artist: Johnny Winter Length: 00:46:56 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.22.mp3, 1.8.1.14.22.wav (Box 14, Cassette 22)
      - [Wire Train] Nina Hagen, Wire Train/In A Chamber, 1:21:29; Artist: Nina Hagen Length: 01:21:2 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.32.mp3, 1.8.1.12.32.wav (Box 12, Cassette 32)
      - [WXLO] John Lennon/Yoko Ono RKO Interview-12/14/80 WXLO NYC Part 1 and 2, Artist: WXLO Length: 01:29:05 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.23.mp3, 1.8.1.14.23.wav (Box 14, Cassette 23)
      - [WXLO] John Lennon/Yoko Ono RKO Interview-12/14/80 WXLO NYC Part 3 and 4, Artist: WXLO Length: 01:20:40 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.24.mp3, 1.8.1.14.24.wav (Box 14, Cassette 24)
      - [Yo Yo Ma] Bach Suites: v/cello \ Bach Suites: Cello, Artist: Yo Yo Ma Length: 01:34:03 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.25.mp3, 1.8.1.24.25.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for cassette J-Card (Box 14, Cassette 25)
      - [Yo Yo Ma] Bach Cello Suites II/Bach on Wood, Artist: Yo Yo Ma Length: 01:24:54 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.26.mp3, 1.8.1.14.26.wav See folder 1.8.1.6.17 for cassette J-Card (Box 14, Cassette 26)
      - [Zappa] Philip Glass, June Pointer 5/83 NYC. Zappa 6/15/83 CBS-D, Artist: Zappa Length: 00:59:09 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.12.32.mp3, 1.8.1.12.32.wav (Box 12, Cassette 32)
      - [Zevon] Zevon EA/LA, Artist: Zevon Length: 00:41:15 Type: Radio File Names: 1.8.1.14.27.mp3, 1.8.1.14.27.wav (Box 14, Cassette 27)
      - No Label, Artist: Unknown Length: 00:04:24 Type: Music File Names: 1.8.1.14.28.mp3, 1.8.1.14.28.wav (Box 14, Cassette 28)
      - No Label, Artist: Unknown Note: Cassette does not play (Box 14, Cassette 29)
      - No Label, Artist: Unknown Note: Cassette does not play (Box 14, Cassette 30)
      - #80741 CR#60 Marist 1998-01, Note: Cassette is too large to play in traditiona cassette player (Box 14, Cassette 31)
      - #80741 CR#61 Marist Mollt + Steve/ Lake Wash + Bella/ Olympics Moon 4A ltr font/J Grri Lte Anne Paddlers on Lake Wash 1998-03, Note: Cassette is too large to play in traditiona cassette player (Box 14, Cassette 32)
      - #80741 CR#62 Marist 1998-02, Note: Cassette is too large to play in traditiona cassette player (Box 14, Cassette 33)
      - #80741 CR#63 Marist ATF 131 tour 2002 04, Note: Cassette is too large to play in traditiona cassette player (Box 14, Cassette 34)
      - #80741 CR#64 Marist Bella; Victoria, Evan Radi, NY Elex, 'Elvis Apt"; Sara + Elander; Dara Alparse, Lie Friend; Sara Sones; Cornwall XMAS, Note: Cassette is too large to play in traditiona cassette player (Box 14, Cassette 35)
      - #80741 CR#65 Marist Trip east N. Mex- Emmt NYC, Ard _ Lydia; Fred and Rhoder, Note: Cassette is too large to play in traditiona cassette player (Box 14, Cassette 36)
      - #80741 CR#66 MaristATF Nelnt Cape Lize -2002, Note: Cassette is too large to play in traditiona cassette player (Box 14, Cassette 37)
      - #80741 CR#67 Marist Cape Lizl 2002, Note: Cassette is too large to play in traditiona cassette player (Box 14, Cassette 38)
      - #80741 CR#68 Marist Work (Box 14, Cassette 39)
      - Cassette J-Cards A-E (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Cassette J-Cards G-M (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Cassette J-Cards O-Y (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Subseries 1.8.2 Open Reel Tapes
      The Three Pointer Sisters
      - Tape 001: On Record Episodes (Tape 001)
      - Tape 002: On Record Episodes (Tape 002)
      - Tape 003: FAA Flight Crash Recording of News Segment (Tape 003)
      - Tape 004: Mitch Clarvit (Tape 004)
      - Tape 005: Interview, Unknown (Tape 005)
      - Tape 006: Art Athens, news story (Tape 006)
      - Tape 007: Space Shuttle launch news reel (Tape 007)
      - Tape 008: Interview, The Knockouts (Tape 008)
      - Tape 009: Interview (Tape 009)
      - Tape 010: On Record (Tape 010)
      - Tape 011: On Record (Tape 011)
      - Tape 012: Interview (Tape 012)
      - Tape 013: On Record (Tape 013)
      - Tape 014: Newsreel (Tape 014)
      - Tape 015: Blank (Tape 015)
      - Tape 016: On Record (Tape 016)
      - Tape 017: Demo Recording (Tape 017)
      - Tape 018: On Record (Tape 018)
      - Tape 019: On Record (Tape 019)
      - Tape 020: Holiday Wishes from Military Personel (Tape 020)
      - Tape 021: Christmas interviews with soldiers (Tape 021)
      - Tape 022: Music, demo tape (Tape 022)
      - Tape 023: Music, demo tape? (Tape 023)
      - Tape 024: Music, demo tape? (Tape 024)
      - Tape 025: On Record (Tape 025)
      - Tape 026: On Record (Tape 026)
      - Tape 027: On Record (Tape 027)
      - Tape 028: On Record (Tape 028)
      - Tape 029: Demo tape, Mitch Clarvit (Tape 029)
      - Tape 030: News Reel (Tape 030)
      - Tape 031: On Record (Tape 031)
      - Tape 032: Blank (Tape 032)
      - Tape 033: On Record (Tape 033)
      - Tape 034: On Recoerd (Tape 034)
      - Tape 035: Music, Demo tape? Synth music (Tape 035)
      - Tape 036: On the plane (Tape 036)
      - Tape 037: Music, Demo tape? Folk (Tape 037)
      - Tape 038: Music, Demo tape? (Tape 038)
      - Tape 039: On Record (Tape 039)
      - Tape 040: On Record (Tape 040)
      - Tape 041: Music, demo tape? (Tape 041)
      - Tape 042: On Record (Tape 042)
      - Tape 043: Music, Demo Tape? (Tape 043)
      - Tape 044: News Reel, CBS, Space shuttle: Challenger (Tape 044)
      - Tape 045: On Record (Tape 045)
      - Tape 046: Between the lines, Ted Nugent (Tape 046)
      - Tape 047: Fleet street group answering machine (Tape 047)
      - Tape 048: Music, Demo tape? (Tape 048)
      - Tape 049: News reel, Sgt. Peppers Premier (Tape 049)
      - Tape 050: On Record (Tape 050)
      - Tape 051: News promos (Tape 051)
      - Tape 052: Music, Demo tape? (Tape 052)
      - Tape 053: Music, Demo Tape? (Tape 053)
      - Tape 054: Music, Backing track? Techno (Tape 054)
      - Tape 055: Music, Demo Tape? (Tape 055)
      - Tape 056: Music (Tape 056)
      - Tape 057: Music (Tape 057)
      - Tape 058: Radio promos (Tape 058)
      - Tape 059: On Record (Tape 059)
      - Tape 060: Music, Demo tape, Mitch Clarvit (Tape 060)
      - Tape 061: Music, demo tape? (Tape 061)
      - Tape 062: On Record (Tape 062)
      - Tape 063: On Record (Tape 063)
      - Tape 064: Music (Tape 064)
      - Tape 065: Music, demo tape? (Tape 065)
      - Tape 066: Challenger explosion (Tape 066)
      - Tape 067: Music samples (Tape 067)
      - Tape 068: On Record (Tape 068)
      - Tape 069: John Lennon Death (Tape 069)
      - Tape 070: On Record (Tape 070)
      - Tape 071: Blank (Tape 071)
      - Tape 072: On Record (Tape 072)
      - Tape 073: On Record (Tape 073)
      - Tape 074: On Record (Tape 074)
      - Tape 075: Peter Bekker, Between the Lines (Tape 075)
      - Tape 076: Blank (Tape 076)
      - Tape 077: On Record (Tape 077)
      - Tape 078: On Record (Tape 078)
      - Tape 079: Background tracks? (Tape 079)
      - Tape 080: On Record (Tape 080)
      - Tape 081: On Record (Tape 081)
      - Tape 082: Blank (Tape 082)
      - Tape 083: On Record (Tape 083)
      - Tape 084: Blank (Tape 084)
      - Tape 085: Music, relaxing (Tape 085)
      - Tape 086: On Record (Tape 086)
      - Tape 087: Irish Ballads (Tape 087)
      - Tape 088: On Record (Tape 088)
      - Tape 089: Blank (Tape 089)
      - Tape 090: On Record (Tape 090)
      - Tape 091: On Record (Tape 091)
      - Tape 092: Music Sampler, Africa by ToTo (Tape 092)
      - Tape 093: Music snippets, promos (Tape 093)
      - Tape 094: Music (Tape 094)
      - Tape 095: On Record (Tape 095)
      - Tape 096: Music (Tape 096)
      - Tape 097: On Record, Dolly Parton (Tape 097)
      - Tape 098: News Reel (Tape 098)
      - Tape 099: Between the Lines, Lou Gatch (Tape 099)
      - Tape 100: To the airport (Tape 100)
      - Tape 101: Music (Tape 101)
      - Tape 102: Music (Tape 102)
      - Tape 103: Muppets music review/interview (Tape 103)
      - Tape 104: Music (Tape 104)
      - Tape 105: Music, Demo tape? (Tape 105)
      - Tape 106: Interview (Tape 106)
      - Tape 107: Interview/Radio show (Tape 107)
      - Tape 108: Demo Tape, Mitch Clarvit (Tape 108)
      - Tape 109: Radio Special: Stephanie Mills (Tape 109)
      - Tape 110: Music (Tape 110)
      - Tape 111: KCLC Promos (Tape 111)
      - Tape 112: On Record (Tape 112)
      - Tape 113: Background tracks (Tape 113)
      - Tape 114: On Record (Tape 114)
      - Tape 115: On Record (Tape 115)
      - Tape 116: Electronic Sounders Reports (Tape 116)
      - Tape 117: Reggae Music (Tape 117)
      - Tape 118: On Record (Tape 118)
      - Tape 119: Music (Tape 119)
      - Tape 120: Music, background tracks (Tape 120)
      - Tape 121: Music, background tracks (Tape 121)
      - Tape 122: Radio/Music Show (Tape 122)
      - Tape 123: Radio Show, biography (Tape 123)
      - Tape 124: Music (Tape 124)
      - Tape 125: Guitar music (Tape 125)
      - Tape 126: Demo Tape, Mitch Clarvit (Tape 126)
      - Tape 127: On Record (Tape 127)
      - Tape 128: Music (Tape 128)
      - Tape 129: Music radio show (Tape 129)
      - Tape 130: Music, Demo Tape? (Tape 130)
      - Tape 131: Music, Demo Tape? (Tape 131)
      - Tape 132: Music, Demo tape (Tape 132)
      - Tape 133: Music, Album (Tape 133)
      - Tape 134: Weather Report, News (Tape 134)
      - Tape 135: On Record (Tape 135)
      - Tape 136: On Record (Tape 136)
      - Tape 137: On Record (Tape 137)
      - Tape 138: Music, The Beatles (Tape 138)
      - Tape 139: Spoken Poem (Tape 139)
      - Tape 140: Music (Tape 140)
      - Tape 141: Blank (Tape 141)
      - Tape 142: Music (Tape 142)
      - Tape 143: Baby Cooeing Sounds (Tape 143)
      - Tape 144: Music, demo tape? (Tape 144)
      - Tape 145: Blank (Tape 145)
      - Tape 146: Music, Radio News Show (Tape 146)
      - Tape 147: Router Sounds (Tape 147)
      - Tape 148: Radio show about classical music (Tape 148)
      - Tape 149: On Record (Tape 149)
      - Tape 150: On Record (Tape 150)
      - Tape 151: KCLC Editorial by Peter Bekker (Tape 151)
      - Tape 152: Music (Tape 152)
      - Tape 153: On Record (Tape 153)
      - Tape 154: Sounders report (Tape 154)
      - Tape 155: Music Album (Tape 155)
      - Tape 156: Music, radio show (Tape 156)
      - Tape 157: Interview (Tape 157)
      - Tape 158: On Record (Tape 158)
      - Tape 159: On Record (Tape 159)
      - Tape 160: On Record (Tape 160)
      - Tape 161: On Record (Tape 161)
      - Tape 162: On Record (Tape 162)
      - Tape 163: On Record (Tape 163)
  - Subseries 1.9 Electronic Media
    - Fidelipac 2/ 1/2, Media requires specialized tape player to access audio (Box 17)
    - Fidelipac 3, Media requires specialized tape player to access audio (Box 17)
    - Fidelipac 5 1/2, Media requires specialized tape player to access audio (Box 17)
    - Zip 100 Bellaville, 1998; Media requires specialized floppy disk drive to access materials (Box 17)
    - Zip 100 Molly + Steve's Wedding, 1998; Media requires specialized floppy disk drive to access materials (Box 17)
    - Zip 100 Swingside Cornwall NY, 1998; Media requires specialized floppy disk drive to access materials (Box 17)
    - Zip 100 Tea w/ Dip, 1998; Media requires specialized floppy disk drive to access materials (Box 17)
    - Disk FS 98 10/97, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Disk, Unlabelled (Box 17)
    - Video cassette, The Complete Beatles (Box 21)
  - Subseries 1.10 Ephemera
    - Subseries 1.10.1 Clothing
      - Yellow T-Shirt, Screen print " E.S. Wilentz's 8th St. Bookshop *Greenwich Village's Famour Bookshop* A literary landmark since 1947. Three floors of books." (Box 26)
      - White T-Shirt, Screen print "The No-tel Moetal "Whispter Quiert Rooms"" (Box 26)
      - Red T-Shirt, Screen print "Space Suttle Landing Edwards A.F.B. April, 1981" (Box 26)
      - Grey T-Shirt, Screen "Tower Recods New York" (Box 26)
      - White T-Shirt, Screen print "Sky King" (Box 26)
      - Black T-Shirt, Screen print, image of hermit grab (Box 26)
      - White Sweatshirt, Screen print "Hard Rock Café, London" (Box 26)
      - MSN Hat (Box 25)
    - Subseries 1.10.2 Magnets
      - Alaska, State magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Phoenix, Arizona, Arizona state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - San Francisco, San Francisco bridge, California state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - California state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Denver, Colorado, Colorado state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Colorado flag, Colorado state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Atlanta, Georgia, Georgia state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Honolulu, Hawaii, Hawaii state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Chicago my kind of town, Chicago Indianna, Indianna state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Indiana state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Topeka, Kansas, Kansas state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Frankfort Kentucky, Kentucky state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Augusta, Maine, Maine state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Minnesota state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - St. Louis, Missouri, Missouri state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Lincoln, Nebraska, Nebraska state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - Cason City, Nevada, Nevada state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 1)
      - MGM Grand, Las Vegas, Nevada, Nevada state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - Stardust, Las Vegas Strip, Nevada, Nevada state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - New Mexico state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - New Mexico state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - New York state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - Fargo, North Dakota state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - Ohio state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - Seattle, Oregon state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - Texas state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - Tennessee state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 2)
      - Vermont state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 3)
      - Cheyenne, Wyoming state magnet (Box 22, Compartment 3)
      - Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada magnet (Box 22, Compartment 3)
      - Nova Scotia, Canada magnet (Box 22, Compartment 3)
      - Toronto, Canada magnet (Box 22, Compartment 3)
      - Victoria, Canada magnet (Box 22, Compartment 3)